# Akshay K Chaudhari

Over 4.7 Years of experience in SAP Ariba and Materials Management with MBA in Supply Chain Management. Proficient in ARIBA Procurement Module ERP, SAP ECC/S4 Hana IN MM module. Looking to get associated with a progressive organization that gives me the scope to apply my knowledge and skills and involve myself as a part of the team that dynamically works towards the growth of the organization

Email:chaudhari11akshay@gmail.com

Contact No:8149469566

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

- Application development senior analyst Accenture, Pune 05/2023 to till date
- Senior Software Engineer Tech Mahindra Ltd, Pune 04/2022 to 05/2023
- 3) Senior Consultant Birlasoft Limited,Pune 01/2022 to 03/2022
- 4) Associate Business Analyst Infosys, Pune 06/2021 to 01/2022
- 5) Project Engineer RECPDCL, Goa Client: Goa Electricity Department 09/2019 to 06/2021
- Providing backend support for SAP Ariba SCC module & Production support for MM Modules.
- Experienced in Implementations of Ariba functionality as a consultant, Experience with Ariba P2P.
- Core administration and Administration config.
- Analyzing CIG integration issues, Ariba network
- issues, UI issues, CIG Mapping.
- End Users interactions for Issue resolution and Trainings. Analysing the solutions son issues raised by client.
- Solving issues/tickets with moderate and critical impact
- Troubleshooting the issue between CIG and SAP MM backend systems.
- ARIBA.P2P process and Template Configurations in ARIBA. Approval workflow configuration.
- Mass data upload.
- Master Data Creation, Change and display.
- Purchasing Info record for standard, subcontracting, consignment materials procurement.
- Source list maintenance.
- Customizing changes as per client requirement.
- Covering range of all basic functionalities of
- organization enterprise structure plant, purchasing organization, storagelocation and purchasing groups.
- Setting Key fields in material master such as materialgroup, basic material and purchasing value key.

## **SKILLS**

- SAP ARIBA SCC Module.
- SAP MM Module.
- SAP Ariba Upstream and Downstream

## **Technical Tools**

- SAP ARIBA
- SAP MM
- Jira
- Service Now
- LPP

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Managers Choice Award in 2020.Best
- Performer of Q2 2020.

## **CERTIFICATION**

- SAP Ariba Supply Chain Collaboration (Globally Certified)
- SAP Ariba Procurement (Globally Certified)

#### LANGUAGES

English. Hindi, Gujarati, Marathi

# **EDUCATION**

- MBA in Supply Chain Management, Pune University.
- Passed out in 2020 with 65.17%

Bachelor of Engineering in Electrical, North

Maharashtra University

Passed out in 2017 with 65.90%

#### DECLARATION

I Akshay K Chaudhari hereby declare that the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge and belief. I would keep up to your expectations. I would always be keen to work for the organization.

[AKSHAY K CHAUDHARI]